sampleinvitationletter.info 2019-06-05

# Privacy - Sample Invitation Letter

This post was most recently updated on June 5th, 2018

Effective Date: **May 30, 2018**

  1. SampleInvitationLetter.com (“us,” “we,” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of SampleInvitationLetter.com (“the Site”). We created this Website Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to give you insight into our information collection and use practices for people visiting the Site.
  2. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

2.1. TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

(a) Categories of Personally Identifiable Information.  We may collect personally identifiable information from you in one of two manners. The first is if you provide us with your name and email address while signing up for a free ebook to receive email communications from us. The second is if you write a comment to a post and list your name, email address or domain.

(b) Privacy Policy Modifications and Updates. If we modify or update this privacy policy, we will post a notice on the Site. You will have 30 days to consider whether you wish to continue accessing and using the Site pursuant to the updates to the policy. The updates and modifications will not be binding upon you until the 30 day period has passed. After 30 days, your continued use of the Site shall act as an affirmative acceptance of the new privacy policy.

(c) Modification or Removal Process. If you wish to remove or modify any of your personally identifiable information, please contact us using the Contact link on the menu of the Site. You may also remove your information from any mailings by “opting out” as indicated in the mailing.

(d) Effective Date: The effective date shall be May 30, 2018.

(e) Do Not Track Signals.  We do not currently honor “do not track” signals issued by browsers or other third party sources.

(f) Third Party Disclosure. Third Party Tracking: As a matter of transparency, we’ve decided to disclose to you whether third parties can acquire and track your personally identifiable information through our website. Google and other sites listed below can track you through this Site as we use their services for social media and infrastructure purposes. Google participates in the NIA opt out program. You can visit [this link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed) to no longer be tracked by Google and Google properties such as Google Plus. You can also visit the following sites to read their privacy policies and how they track individuals across the web:

Facebook  https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/,

Twitter  <https://twitter.com/privacy>

YouTube – https://www.youtube.com/static?template=privacy_guidelines

You can use programs such as Privacy Badger – <https://www.eff.org/privacybadger> – to further control the collection of information regarding you online.

(g) California Eraser Law. If you are a minor and wish to request the removal of any content you have created and uploaded to the Site, please use the Contact function on the Site to make your request. Please note the removal of content from this Site does not necessarily mean it cannot be found elsewhere on the Internet. Search engines and archive sites regularly index the Internet and make copies of website content.

(h) Google Advertising Cookie and Doubleclick Dart Cookie. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this Site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to various sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy here. http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

2.2. WHAT ADDITIONAL INFORMATION DOES COMPANY COLLECT?

(a) AUTOMATIC COLLECTION. Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Site may also gather anonymous “traffic data” that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.

(b) COOKIES. From time to time, we may use “cookies” to store a small piece of data on your computer during your visit to track how you use our Site. These cookies will track how you use our Site.

  3. USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION

3.1. WHAT DOES COMPANY DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?

(a) PERSONAL INFORMATION. We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law.

(b) ANONYMOUS INFORMATION. We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

(c) USE OF COOKIES. We may use cookies to gather information on where you move about the Site. The purpose of this is to analyze how the Site is performing and the type of information visitors prefer and do not prefer. We do not use cookies for the purpose personalizing our own advertising to you or to allow third party advertisers and partners to do so.

(d) DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Company or its parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates, (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Company or the users of the Site, or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site.

(e) SALE OF INFORMATION. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets, including the information collected through this Site. If Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, your personally identifiable information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.

(f) DMCA CLAIM DISCLOSURES. We comply with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998, better known as the “DMCA”.  Should we receive a claim of copyright infringement, we will comply with the safe harbor requirements of the DMCA. Part of that compliance may require the disclosure of your identity if you are either the allegedly infringing party or the party filing the copyright infringement complaint.

  4. SECURITY

The Site has reasonable security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

  5. SITE AREAS BEYOND COMPANY’S CONTROL

5.1. PUBLIC COMMENTS

The Site includes interactive sections such as commenting areas where you can post comments. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

5.2. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

The Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we have no control over the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

  6. CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES

6.1. CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to this Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database please feel contact us using the Contact link on the menu of the site.
